const e="english",o=200,a=75,t=[{id:522,question:"Though Mr, Iro is our new chairman, he views other members with jaundiced eye, ",option:{a:" He takes a rather forceful position on dealing with his members.",b:"He takes an unfavourable position concerning his members",c:"He takes a sickly view of his members. ",d:"He takes a rather hazy view of his members."},section:" select the option that best explains the Information conveyed In the sentence. ",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2010",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:523,question:"People are not interested in who rules ",option:{a:"People are not ruled by the leaders they want ",b:"People are not concerned about who rules them ",c:"The rulers are not concerned about the people ",d:"People who rule are not interested in the ruled."},section:" select the option that best explains the Information conveyed In the sentence. ",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2010",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:524,question:"It is always good to steer a middle course in whatever one does. ",option:{a:"It is always good to get midway in anything one does. ",b:"It is always good to act with moderation. ",c:"It is always good to move away from the forefront",d:"It is always good to work very hard."},section:" select the option that best explains the Information conveyed In the sentence. ",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2010",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:525,question:"The witness said he had no axe to grind with his brothers.",option:{a:" He had no hatred for the brothers ",b:"He had no axe and therefore stole the matchet ",c:"He had no axe and therefore borrowed their matchet ",d:"He had no vested interest in the brothers."},section:" select the option that best explains the Information conveyed In the sentence. ",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2010",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:526,question:"The footballers moved with their tails between their legs.",option:{a:"They moved happily because they won the match",b:"They were unhappy because they had been despised  by their opponents. ",c:"They were ashamed because they had been defeated ",d:"they moved with their tails between their legs."},section:" select the option that best explains the Information conveyed In the sentence. ",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2010",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:527,question:"The headmaster managed to talk his way out of having  to give a speech ",option:{a:"He delivered a speech despite the difficulty ",b:"He managed to give a speech out of a difficult situation ",c:"He managed to get himself out of a difficult situation",d:"He managed to talk on his way."},section:" select the option that best explains the Information conveyed In the sentence. ",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2010",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:528,question:"As regards the matter, we have crossed the rubicon",option:{a:"We are completely at a toss",b:"We are irrevocably committed ",c:" We are already quaffed",d:"We are perfectly committed.  "},section:" select the option that best explains the Information conveyed In the sentence. ",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2010",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:529,question:"Uche is full of himself ",option:{a:"He is concerted ",b:"He is complete  ",c:"He is a rich man ",d:"He is careful."},section:" select the option that best explains the Information conveyed In the sentence. ",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2010",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:530,question:"As debutants in that tournament, the Super Eagles were up against their first opponents by three goals to nil",option:{a:"The Super Eagles were playing in the tournament for the first time, but they won their match by three goals to nothing ",b:"Though the Super Eagles were rated as the weakest side in the tournament they won their first match by three goals to nil ",c:"Even though the Super Eagles were playing without some of their regulars, they won their match by three goals to nil.",d:"As the best attackers in the match. the Super Eagles easily defeated their opponents by three goals to nothing."},section:" select the option that best explains the Information conveyed In the sentence. ",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2010",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:531,question:"The woman was mournful as her husband was found dead drunk  ",option:{a:"She was sad because her husband was absolutely drunk ",b:"She was apprehensive that her husband would drink again as soon as he recovered from the drunken stupor. ",c:"She was sad because her husband was drunk and always as helpless as a dead  man ",d:"She was mourning because her husband drank and died."},section:" select the option that best explains the Information conveyed In the sentence. ",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2010",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:532,question:"I am optimistic about the Interview though It was a <i>mind- bending</i>  exercise, ",option:{a:"an enervating ",b:"a debilitating",c:"a difficult ",d:"an easy"},section:"choose the option opposite In meaning to the word or phrase In Italics",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2010",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:533,question:"The trader was amused by the  <i>cutthroat</i>  rush for the goods ",option:{a:"worrisome",b:"strange ",c:"lacklustre ",d:"mad"},section:"choose the option opposite In meaning to the word or phrase In Italics",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2010",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:534,question:"The teacher said that All's essay was full of many  <i>redundant</i>  details ",option:{a:"unexplained ",b:"strange",c:"necessary ",d:"useful"},section:"choose the option opposite In meaning to the word or phrase In Italics",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2010",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:535,question:"His father surmounted the  <i>myriad</i>  of obstacles on his way ",option:{a:"most ",b:"few ",c:"all ",d:"many"},section:"choose the option opposite In meaning to the word or phrase In Italics",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2010",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:536,question:"Her  <i>ingenuous</i>  smile drew our attention ",option:{a:"witty",b:" naive ",c:"clever ",d:"arrogant"},section:"choose the option opposite In meaning to the word or phrase In Italics",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2010",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:537,question:"Ndeni gave a  <i>flawless</i>  speech at the party ",option:{a:"a wonderful ",b:"a careless ",c:"an interesting ",d:"an imperfect"},section:"choose the option opposite In meaning to the word or phrase In Italics",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2010",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:538,question:" Beneath Ado's  <i>guff</i>  exterior, he's really very kind-hearted",option:{a:"nice",b:"harsh ",c:"rough ",d:"gentle"},section:"choose the option opposite In meaning to the word or phrase In Italics",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2010",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:539,question:"The captain says sports is being  <i>debased</i>  by commercial sponsorship ",option:{a:"localized ",b:"perverted",c:"elevated ",d:"overvalued"},section:"choose the option opposite In meaning to the word or phrase In Italics",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2010",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:540,question:"Governing a country is not always as  <i>straightforward as</i>  people sometimes imagine.",option:{a:"complicated",b:"troublesome   ",c:"untoward   ",d:"Irksome"},section:"choose the option opposite In meaning to the word or phrase In Italics",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2010",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:541,question:"The crowd was very  <i>receptive </i>  to the speaker's suggestion ",option:{a:"disobedient ",b:"repellent ",c:"alert",d:"Hostile"},section:"choose the option opposite In meaning to the word or phrase In Italics",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2010",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:542,question:"There was a general  <i>acquiescence</i>  on the new drug law ",option:{a:"resistance ",b:"discrepancy ",c:"compromise",d:"agreement"},section:"choose the option opposite In meaning to the word or phrase In Italics",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2010",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:543,question:"Aisha seems to feel  <i>ambivalent</i>  about her future",option:{a:"decisive ",b:"anxious ",c:"ambitious ",d:"inconsiderate"},section:"choose the option opposite In meaning to the word or phrase In Italics",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2010",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:544,question:"The report of the committee contained a  <i>plethora</i>  of details",option:{a:" shortage ",b:"simplicity ",c:"multitude",d:" spectrum"},section:"choose the option opposite In meaning to the word or phrase In Italics",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2010",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:545,question:"The weather was still very  <i>heavy and sultry </i> ",option:{a:"wintry and shadowy ",b:"cold and friendly ",c:"cloudy and thundery",d:"hot and uncomfortable"},section:"choose the option opposite In meaning to the word or phrase In Italics",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2010",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:546,question:"Ada gave her husband a look that made words  <i>superfluous</i> ",option:{a:"redundant ",b:"spurious ",c:"unnecessary",d:" scanty."},section:"choose the option opposite In meaning to the word or phrase In Italics",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2010",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:547,question:"A political  <i>impasse</i>  does not offer the best opportunity for merrymaking ",option:{a:"manifesto ",b:"party ",c:"gridlock",d:" rally"},section:"choose the option nearest  in meaning to the word or phrase in Italics.",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2010",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:548,question:"We were all  <i>enthusiastic</i>  as we awaited the result of the election ",option:{a:"bemused ",b:"agitated ",c:"elated",d:"nervous"},section:"choose the option nearest  in meaning to the word or phrase in Italics.",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2010",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:549,question:"The uniform makes the guards look  <i>absurd</i>  ",option:{a:"dirty",b:"smart ",c:"sensible",d:"ridiculous"},section:"choose the option nearest  in meaning to the word or phrase in Italics.",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2010",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:550,question:"The law is often  <i>tardy</i>  in reacting to changing attitude",option:{a:" quick",b:"low ",c:"exclusive ",d:"generous"},section:"choose the option nearest  in meaning to the word or phrase in Italics.",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2010",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:551,question:"Isa and llu  <i>ate sumptuous</i>  meals on their brother's wedding day",option:{a:"expensive ",b:"foreign ",c:"insipid",d:"cheap"},section:"choose the option nearest  in meaning to the word or phrase in Italics.",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2010",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:552,question:"Kaltume  <i>crouched</i>  over the papers on her desk ",option:{a:"wrote on  ",b:"stood on ",c:"walked over",d:"bent over"},section:"choose the option nearest  in meaning to the word or phrase in Italics.",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2010",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:553,question:"The <i> panacea</i>  for a country's economic mess lies in systematic planning and hard work ",option:{a:"cure  ",b:"hope",c:"foresight ",d:"trouble"},section:"choose the option nearest  in meaning to the word or phrase in Italics.",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2010",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:554,question:"Thousands of workers have been victims of  <i>retrenchment</i>  since the military came back to power.",option:{a:"unemployment ",b:"trench mentality ",c:"suffering ",d:"increase in penury"},section:"choose the option nearest  in meaning to the word or phrase in Italics.",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2010",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:555,question:"The principal gave his speech   <i>off hand</i>  at the sports  meeting ",option:{a:"calmly ",b:"Beautifully ",c:"unconcerned",d:"unprepared"},section:"choose the option nearest  in meaning to the word or phrase in Italics.",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2010",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:556,question:"Jankoli was dressed in an old  <i>assortment</i>  of clothes",option:{a:"avalanche ",b:"homogeneity ",c:"sameness",d:"melange"},section:"choose the option nearest  in meaning to the word or phrase in Italics.",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2010",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:557,question:"The girl's father was  <i>astounded</i>  to see her appear from the shrine ",option:{a:"collected ",b:"overwhelmed",c:"embarrassed ",d:"astonished"},section:"choose the option nearest  in meaning to the word or phrase in Italics.",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2010",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:558,question:"The director's remark was extremely  <i>apposite</i>  to the issue being discussed ",option:{a:"appropriate",b:"inconsequential ",c:"emphatic ",d:"adequate"},section:"choose the option nearest  in meaning to the word or phrase in Italics.",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2010",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:559,question:"Her reputation is without a  <i>blemish </i> ",option:{a:"struggle",b:"problem ",c:"fault ",d:"blessing"},section:"choose the option nearest  in meaning to the word or phrase in Italics.",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2010",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:560,question:"Ugo is  <i>eligible</i>  for the post of secretary ",option:{a:"nominated",b:"invited",c:"qualified ",d:"intelligent"},section:"choose the option nearest  in meaning to the word or phrase in Italics.",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2010",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:561,question:"This is an  <i>abridged</i> version of No Longer at Ease",option:{a:"an outdated    ",b:"an enlarged ",c:"an illustrated ",d:"a shortened"},section:"choose the option nearest  in meaning to the word or phrase in Italics.",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2010",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:562,question:"Lemoti ………..",option:{a:"is gifted only not ",b:"is only not gifted  ",c:"not only ",d:"is only gifted"},section:"choose the option that best completes the gap(s)",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2010",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:563,question:"He can recall the important dates in the nation's history; it is interesting to listen as he rattles…….",option:{a:"off",b:"over",c:"up   ",d:"out"},section:"choose the option that best completes the gap(s)",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2010",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:564,question:"The boy told his mother",option:{a:"that was the girl he told her about ",b:"that was the girl I told you about her",c:"that was the girl I told her about ",d:"that is the girl he told her about"},section:"choose the option that best completes the gap(s)",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2010",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:565,question:"Last Monday his father asked me, .......",option:{a:"if' had come some days before ",b:"if I had come the day before",c:"did you come yesterday ",d:"had I come yesterday"},section:"choose the option that best completes the gap(s)",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2010",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:566,question:"His wife was badly injured in the fracas, but I think  she will pull",option:{a:"up  ",b:"over ",c:"through ",d:"back"},section:"choose the option that best completes the gap(s)",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2010",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:567,question:"A wide range of options",option:{a:"is ",b:"were   ",c:"are",d:" was"},section:"choose the option that best completes the gap(s)",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2010",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:568,question:"One of the women who .... in the premises.... been  ordered to quit ",option:{a:"sells/have ",b:"sell/has  ",c:"sell/have",d:"sells/has"},section:"choose the option that best completes the gap(s)",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2010",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:569,question:"The new trade agreement should facilitate…..... ",option:{a:"more economic rapid growth  ",b:"economic more rapid  growth ",c:"rapid economic more growth   ",d:"more rapid economic growth."},section:"choose the option that best completes the gap(s)",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2010",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:570,question:"The principal said that he was pleased......... my effort.",option:{a:" on ",b:"of ",c:"with",d:"about"},section:"choose the option that best completes the gap(s)",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2010",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:571,question:"Paper is made…….. wood pulp ",option:{a:"on ",b:"of ",c:"from ",d:"with"},section:"choose the option that best completes the gap(s)",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2010",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:572,question:"Long after everyone…... the hall, Obi still sat inside.",option:{a:"left",b:"is leaving ",c:"has left",d:"had left"},section:"choose the option that best completes the gap(s)",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2010",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:573,question:"They are the.... dresses ",option:{a:"babys' ",b:"baby ",c:"babies",d:"babies'"},section:"choose the option that best completes the gap(s)",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2010",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:574,question:"The politician was sent …….. exile",option:{a:"onto ",b:"into",c:"on ",d:"to"},section:"choose the option that best completes the gap(s)",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2010",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:575,question:"When we looked up, we …….... the plane some miles away. ",option:{a:"site ",b:"cited ",c:"sited ",d:"sighted"},section:"choose the option that best completes the gap(s)",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2010",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:576,question:"Vital... is still spread ……..... word of mouth in most villages in Africa. ",option:{a:"information/from  ",b:"information/with",c:"information/by ",d:"information/through "},section:"choose the option that best completes the gap(s)",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2010",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:577,question:"Western  education is one of the ... of colonial rule",option:{a:"legacies  ",b:"evidence ",c:"remnants ",d:"inheritance "},section:"choose the option that best completes the gap(s)",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2010",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:578,question:"The Federal Government has .... child trafficking ",option:{a:"postulated  ",b:"projected ",c:"prescribed ",d:"proscribed"},section:"choose the option that best completes the gap(s)",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2010",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:579,question:"The man was happy that his son confessed his guilt and so the others were .... ",option:{a:"implicated",b:"accused ",c:"punished ",d:"Exonerated"},section:"choose the option that best completes the gap(s)",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2010",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:580,question:"  Based on the facts before me, I have no alternative...........to hold you responsible ",option:{a:"only ",b:"as ",c:"than ",d:"but"},section:"choose the option that best completes the gap(s)",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2010",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:581,question:"Many people would always find reasons to ... the law",option:{a:"arrogate ",b:"debase  ",c:" circumvent ",d:"circumspect"},section:"choose the option that best completes the gap(s)",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2010",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:582,question:"c<u>oup</u> ",option:{a:"whup  ",b:"shoot ",c:"couple ",d:"scout"},section:"choose the option that has the same vowel sound as the one represented by the letters underlined.",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2010",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:583,question:"ind<u>i</u>ct ",option:{a:"bright   ",b:"fish ",c:"pick ",d:"brick"},section:"choose the option that has the same vowel sound as the one represented by the letters underlined.",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2010",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:584,question:"r<u>oa</u>red ",option:{a:"towered ",b:"coast ",c:"brought ",d:"rod"},section:"choose the option that has the same vowel sound as the one represented by the letters underlined.",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2010",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:585,question:"shea<u>th </u>",option:{a:"bathe ",b:"length ",c:"months ",d:"paths"},section:"choose the option that has the same consonant sound as the one represented by the letter(s) underlined",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2010",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:586,question:"<u>h</u>igh ",option:{a:"what  ",b:"honest ",c:"who ",d:"vehicle"},section:"choose the option that has the same consonant sound as the one represented by the letter(s) underlined",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2010",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:587,question:"o<u>f </u>course  ",option:{a:"plough ",b:"dough ",c:"over ",d:"orphan"},section:"choose the option that has the same consonant sound as the one represented by the letter(s) underlined",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2010",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:588,question:"boys ",option:{a:"stays  ",b:" moist ",c:"noise ",d:"elbows"},section:"choose the option that rhymes with the given word.",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2010",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:589,question:"shine ",option:{a:"clean ",b:"fine ",c:" machine ",d:"lain"},section:"choose the option that rhymes with the given word.",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2010",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:590,question:"seer ",option:{a:"snare   ",b:"spare",c:"spear ",d:"square"},section:"choose the option that rhymes with the given word.",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2010",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:591,question:"political ",option:{a:"politiCAL  ",b:"POlitical",c:"poliTlcal",d:"poLltical"},section:"choose the most appropriate stress pattern from the options. The stressed syllable are written in capital letter(s)",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2010",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:592,question:"satisfactory ",option:{a:"satisfacTORY  ",b:"saTISfactory",c:"SATisfactory ",d:"satisFACtory"},section:"choose the most appropriate stress pattern from the options. The stressed syllable are written in capital letter(s)",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2010",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:593,question:"captivity ",option:{a:"captiviTY   ",b:"captiVIty  ",c:"capTlvity",d:"CAPtivity"},section:"choose the most appropriate stress pattern from the options. The stressed syllable are written in capital letter(s)",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2010",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:594,question:"EMEKA finished his home work yesterday ",option:{a:"Was Emeka helped to do his home work? ",b:"Did Emeka do his home work yesterday?",c:"When did Emeka finish his home work? ",d:"Who finished his home work yesterday"},section:"the word in capital letters has the <i>emphatic stress</i>. Choose the option to which the given sentence relates",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2010",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:595,question:"Taiwo SAILED to London",option:{a:"Did Taiwo fly to London?",b:" Did Taiwo sail to Brazil",c:"Did Taiwo sail to London?",d:"Where did Taiwo sail to?"},section:"the word in capital letters has the <i>emphatic stress</i>. Choose the option to which the given sentence relates",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2010",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:596,question:"My bag is made of LEATHER ",option:{a:"Whose bag is made of leather? ",b:"Is my bag made of polythene? ",c:"Is Abu's bag made of leather? ",d:"Is my bag made of leather"},section:"the word in capital letters has the <i>emphatic stress.</i> Choose the option to which the given sentence relates",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2010",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"}],s={subject:e,status:200,total:75,data:t};export{t as data,s as default,o as status,e as subject,a as total};
